[music]
>> Hello angels. I fear these summer ween
propaganda has been getting to me
because as a die hard summer girly
myself, I never want to like rush the
end of summer and I still don't. Like
we're so not doing that. However, I have
been just having like a hankering for
fall vibes. I just painted my nails
brown last night. This is the first dark
color I've done like all year. Got some
new cute fall clothes. I'm just feeling
really excited for it. So, I thought
today we could just embrace fall for a
day and have a summer ween inspired day.
I don't know if you could tell, but I
did do my makeup moodier than usual. I
love these like blush lipsticks from
Merit. They're like sheer, but they have
a really pretty color. It's like a
little powdery matte finish and then
I'll like pop a little gloss on top of
that. Here's the current outfit. This
whole outfit is from Cider. My burgundy
sneakers because I feel like boots would
make this feel full fall, but like low
sneakers like this feels good for
summer, too. This is Afternoon Delight
from Replica. This was like one of my
favorite fall scents last year. It
smells like baked goods and a French
cafe. Perfect for today, but I don't
want too much. And here's my bag of the
day. Oh my gosh, it's so gorgeous. We're
going out shopping. My mom's coming with
me. Like we're both so excited. to see
whatever cute fall things we can find. I
know specific stores actually have
summer ween collections. I'm just
excited to see what's out, so let's get
going.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Here's a fall butter dish.
Is this Le Creuset? It looks like it.
Wow. [laughter]
>> You're right.
>> There's a few fall themed mugs, but I
don't love those. Charlie Brown is cute.
Okay, that's kind of adorable.
>> They do have some little soft bears.
>> Aw, are those dogs? Those are cute.
Actually, would that fit me? That's
beautiful. That's a five to a six. I'm a
six and a half, unfortunately. We have
some kind of fall flowers up there. I
feel like I already have some though.
Pillows, which are always my favorite,
but I feel like these are a little dark
in color. I'm going for more of a pink
and orange fall vibe, as you can
probably guess.
Not really my vibe. We're going to have
to come back in a little bit, but I
think the other stores are going to be
more promising.
>> [music]
>> Okay, just left TJ Maxx. The only thing
is there was pretty much nothing fall
related there. Honestly, I was surprised
cuz I feel like the brands and stores,
they're like so ahead of it, you know?
Like I expect to walk into a store in
August. I'm like I'm already expecting
fall. Like they're always so early on
the season, so
>> Halloween stuff.
>> There was some Halloween stuff, but it
wasn't it wasn't cute. I was wanting
like pink, orange. So, we're now at the
mall, going to Lush. I think there's
like an Aerie and American Eagle here,
and I know I've seen them having like
Summerween collections. So, hoping we
can find some better things cuz
currently I've gotten nothing. This car
is like a billion degrees. It's really
not feeling like fall vibes right now.
>> [music]
[music]
>> It's cute. me.
>> Look at that silver sparkling moon.
>> [music]
[music]
>> They thankfully did have some Halloween
stuff out at Lush, so that's so
exciting. I think we're going to go to
Aerie now and hopefully they have some
cute stuff as well. That's really cute
actually.
>> Is that one little
>> hearts? Wait, that's really pretty.
>> It looks like it's cotton, too.
>> Wow, look at that ribbon.
>> I know, that's really pretty.
>> [music]
>> Which socks do you like the best?
There's Snoopy, this little pumpkin
that's cute.
>> Jimmy
>> Which one should I get?
>> Look at that eating watermelon.
>> [laughter]
>> That's like summer-ween.
>> Like look at the aqua color, [music] but
then look at these little ghosts in the
background.
>> Mhm.
>> I kind of am drawn to this one.
>> That's a
>> [music]
>> darling.
>> I always like to leave Smell that one.
>> Leaves?
>> Smells like sugar. Smells like sugar
cookies.
>> Which one is that?
>> That's called Fall Amazing Cashmere.
That's probably sweet.
>> Mhm.
Too sweet.
>> Beautiful. Those are pretty designs.
>> [music]
[music]
>> We just finished up at the mall. We did
hit a few jackpots. Like American Eagle
did have a little display out. Bath &
Body Works definitely had [music] fall
stuff out. I went to Victoria's Secret.
I was hoping they would have like a
bunch of the kind of spooky underwear,
but they only had a few and I wasn't
really loving them. But, I bought some
other stuff, and then they ended up
giving us like a dog to blind box open.
And if we get the gold one, we get a
$100 gift get a $100 gift card. I hope
we get I feel like that one is cuter
than that.
>> I like that guy.
>> Okay, they probably won't all be good,
but these are the options.
>> Okay, I guess I'll guess that it's this
one, and you guess that one.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay, let's see.
>> Oh, it's in a bag.
>> Oh.
It's kind of purpley.
>> I mean, it's purple.
>> It sort of fits the fall vibe.
>> You wanted this one.
>> Wow.
What a fun little treat. Now, onto
Barnes & Noble. I don't really need new
books. Hopefully, just like limit myself
to like one.
>> You want to get a
>> I mean, you have not been in your
reading era.
>> No, but I do want to look at the
stationery.
>> Yeah, let's see what they have. That
looks like it's giving fall vibes, but
that looks pretty corny to me.
You know, I've read her other two books.
I wonder if I should read this one. I do
like a mystery. Yeah. Is this one new?
>> [music]
>> Not going to lie, guys, I'm a little
exhausted from shopping like literally
all day, but last stop of the day,
Michaels. I know Michaels is going to
have like good Halloween and fall stuff,
but I'm hoping to find some cute like
pink and orange aesthetic Halloween
stuff. So, if we can find that, I might
pick up a few things. They're decked
out. They're decked. I see this is like
spooky vibe. I want cozy vibe.
I'm sure I can use [music] that
somewhere.
>> Do you need anything?
>> Mhm.
>> Got it.
>> Thanks.
>> [music]
>> I think I bought this specific thing
last year. I actually really liked the
way it looked. Oh, there's like little
tiny cute things.
>> I know.
>> And pine cones.
And moss. That's kind of cute.
>> Look at that cute little market.
>> That is cute. Oh my goodness. What in
the world? Is there a cinnamon
[laughter] roll? This is kind of insane.
Like is this for real? It's Hall time,
guys. That was literally so much fun.
Like is there anything better than a
shopping day with your mom? Let's start
with American Eagle. I never shop at
American Eagle. However, they were one
of the only stores doing the Summerween
thing and I kind of wanted to see. Then
when I saw these pajamas, which are 100%
cotton and they're Snoopy, I was like,
yeah. Yeah, we're getting them. so
perfectly Summerween because they're a
short set. So they're obviously not too
hot and the cotton feels so light and
airy. And I decided to get some socks as
well. These are always just perfect to
wear throughout the fall. So like this
pair has little pumpkins and bows and I
really liked these ones that have an
embroidered pumpkin on them. Next,
Barnes & Noble. We renewed our
membership for the year, so we got to
pick a tote and I picked this green one,
which feels very like moody fall in my
opinion. I picked The Guest List by Lucy
Foley. Like I said, I've read The Paris
Apartment and The Hunting Party. And I
enjoyed both of them. Mystery's like one
of my favorite genre of movies and
books. Like I love thrillers and just
like suspense. Always down for a who
done it. Let me know if you've read this
book. Then, Victoria's Secret. We have
the little dog I showed you. This was
such a fun thing. I love that they're
bringing these back. I got some of the
pink like boy shorts a few months ago
because they're so comfy to wear to bed
and I wanted to see if they have more of
that. They did have some. So like I got
a few few pairs of these and some other
cute underwear as well. Next, Michael's,
which undoubtedly had the best
selection. They still didn't have a ton
of like pink fall stuff yet, but I did
find this pink pumpkin and a smaller
pink pumpkin. These will be perfect for
putting around my room this year. I also
saw these pumpkin candles, which I
thought were so adorable and some
pumpkin lights. Then we have Lush. I did
stock up on my favorite fall scents,
which are sticky dates. I got the shower
gel and the body scrub. I love both of
these so much. They truly do smell quite
sweet, but like I love sweet scents. It
really smells like caramely brown sugar,
molasses. After I use this, my boyfriend
says I smell like a s'more. So,
honestly, I love it. It's gold. It's
really pretty. I decided to get this
soap. It's just so up my alley. Like, I
couldn't [music] resist. I think it kind
of melted in the car. It's a little moon
soap. I love it. It actually smells
really nice, too. Yay, I can't wait to
take a self-care shower tonight. We're
making veggie pot pie for dinner. It's
going to be like the most perfect cozy
dinner ever. My mom is kind of prepping
that right now, which is so nice of her.
So, I'm going to take a quick shower,
get changed into some comfy clothes, and
then we'll have a nice dinner and do
some baking.
>> [music]
>> Sauteed the celery and onions. Put the
flour to make a roux. Now, I'm pouring
all of this in there. Carrots, sweet
potatoes,
green beans,
tofu,
and beans.
>> [music]
>> It seems good.
Those are my favorite soaps.
Isn't it so weird that
>> Yeah, luscious.
>> [music]
>> I hate wearing brand new clothes without
washing them first. I will not be
sleeping [music] in these, but I just
like for the sake of the video and the
summer mean vibes today, I want to wear
these for the evening. And I just threw
my hair in some [music] braids to like
get it out of the way for tonight. But
my boyfriend is coming over tonight. I
want to make some pumpkin bread. I know
it's a little ambitious because we've
already had a full day, but like I
really want to make pumpkin bread. We're
going to eat some dinner, make some
pumpkin bread, and then it chill
tonight. Really want to watch Obsession
with my boyfriend Yoni. We have been
wanting to watch it.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Smells like pumpkin.
Hey Debel.
Can I have some of the batter?
>> You're not supposed to eat raw flour.
You can have it when it's cooked.
>> So I can't have raw eggs or raw flour or
raw what else?
>> Yeah, basically raw anything. Um
especially with the way our FDA is at
the moment.
>> [music]
[music]
>> This is my actual face after watching
that movie.
Because what did I just watch? Yoni just
went home. I'm a little scared to sleep
in my room tonight, to be honest. If you
guys have seen Obsession, comment your
thoughts. It was an incredible movie.
The actress, I've been seeing a ton of
stuff about her lately. Oh, she did
amazing. Like she did amazing. It was
such a a movie with great themes, but it
was like so triggering on so many
levels. As an emetophobia girly, yeah,
that movie was not safe for me. We were
eating as we were watching it. You can
just you can never unsee some of those
images. I had a lot of fun embracing
fall like a little bit early, but I am
ready to kind of get back to like summer
vibes for the next just maybe like 2
weeks. Squeeze all the life that I can
out of summer, but this has been really
fun to just cosplay fall for a day. I
really hope you enjoyed coming along
with me. Comment this emoji if you
watched up until the end of the video.
Feel free to comment your fall video
requests. What would you like to see on
my channel this fall? And I will see you
in my next video. Mwah. Bye, guys.
>> [music]
[music]